eastessence.com 2012-09-20

# Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy and the Security of Your Personal Information is Very Important to Us**

East Essence and Kilam Inc., value our customers and visitors to our Websites and respect your concerns about the privacy of your personal information and data security. Our Privacy and Security Policy (the "Privacy Policy") is intended to protect your privacy and provide you with a safe and secure experience in fashion, style and shopping. This Privacy Policy applies to our Website, namely, [www.eastessence.com](http://www.eastessence.com/) . This Privacy Policy protects consumers providing information through our Websites and stores and is not designed to protect business information. By using our Website or providing information to us at our stores, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information. In addition to reviewing our Privacy Policy, you should also read our Terms of Use for our Websites. Your use of our Websites constitutes your agreement to its terms and conditions.

**Our Privacy Policy Will Change Over Time**

Because we continue to develop our Website and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, our policies will change over time. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy from time to time to stay abreast of our most current privacy policy practices. If you are a registered user of our Websites, we may notify you by email of material changes to our Privacy Policy using the most current email address you have provided to us. Your continued access and use of our Websites will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to our Privacy Policy.

**Summary of Our Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy explains and summarizes how we collect, use and protect your personal information as you interact with us online and through our customer and technical support. This Privacy Policy explains: 

  * What information EastEssence gathers from users of our Website. 
  * How EastEssence uses the personal information that you share with us and that we learn about you because of our relationship. 
  * How EastEssence uses "cookies" and "IP Addresses." 
  * What personal information, if any, EastEssence  may share about you with others and the conditions that protect your information if it must be shared. 
  * What kind of security measures EastEssence takes to protect your information from loss or disclosure and how EastEssence will inform you in the event of a security breach. 
  * The circumstances under which you can access your personal information you have shared with EastEssence  and have that information corrected, restrict EastEssence's use of that information, and even have it removed from our records. 
  * Other things you should know about privacy and EastEssence.

**The Type of Information our Websites and Stores Collect About You**

EastEssence collects information that you provide to us or that we learn about you from your use of our Website. We receive and store information you enter on our Website, or give to us in any other way. For example, you may provide information to us when you register with our Websites, sign-in, search, add items to your shopping cart, pay for an item, participate in a survey, contest or promotion, apply for a job, request to receive our marketing materials, or communicate with EastEssence's customer service. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, phone number, email address, payment card information, and personal shopping and product preferences. In applying for a job with us, you may provide to us your your name, address, phone number, email address, previous work experience, references and other personal information about your background and experience.

We also automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit our Websites. We might also receive information about you from other sources, such as in providing you special offers that we think will be of interest, and we may add that information to our account information.

**How EastEssence Uses Information About You**

We use information we have collected about you to provide you with the very best shopping experience, the most current fashion clothing and accessories, and personal style news. **We do not sell your personal information to third parties for any reason.** We do not disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties, or to our affiliates, who may want to offer you their own products and services unless you have requested or authorized us to do so.

We may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of EastEssence where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction you authorized or perform some other activity you have asked us to do.

We may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of EastEssence with whom we have contracted to perform services on our behalf. All companies that act on our behalf are contractually obligated to keep the personal information we provide to them confidential and to use the personal information we share only to provide the services we ask them to perform. 

We may disclose personal information about our customers as permitted or required by law, such as in connection with a subpoena or similar legal process, or in connection with a merger, acquisition or bankruptcy, as discussed further below. We may disclose information about you to protect against fraud and other crimes and to enforce our contracts with you. 

We try to provide you with the information you need to make informed reasonable choices with respect to how our Websites uses or shares your information. EastEssence collects and uses personal information from you in several ways: 

  * **Website usage.** EastEssence or EastEssence's authorized service providers may observe activities, preferences and transactional data (such as your IP address, browser type and operating system) relating to your use of our Websites. We may use this collected or logged information in order to provide better service, to facilitate our customers' use of the website, to track usage of the website, and to address security hazards. EastEssence, or one of EastEssence's authorized service providers, may use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout our Websites for EastEssence's internal analysis.
  * **Online Transactions.** We collect information about you when you shop on our website. You may visit our site without registering, but if you wish to add merchandise to your shopping cart, create a wish list or use other special features offered on our site, you will need to provide us with certain information, including your name, address, phone number and email address, to open an account with us. We will assist you in creating a user id and a password to protect your account information. Similarly, if you wish to apply online for a job position with us, you will be required to submit relevant information about your background and experience.

**Our Security Practices**

Our internal data security policies restrict access to customers' personal information to authorized employees. Authorized employees may use our customers' personal information for EastEssence business purposes only. Our employees are bound by EastEssence policies that require them to maintain the confidentiality of our customers' personal information. Employees who violate these requirements are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination. 

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that are designed to guard our customers' personal information. For example, for the security of your online visit to our Websites, we may make use of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and/or authentication procedures. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, EastEssence cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In the event of a breach of the confidentiality or security of your personal information, we will notify you as necessary and to the extent possible so you can take appropriate protective steps. Unless you indicate otherwise, we may notify you under such circumstances using the email address you provided to us when you registered with our Websites.

**What are Cookies and How Does our Websites Use Them?**

We may use "cookies" to collect or log certain information. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website stores on a personal computer and which it can later retrieve. We may use cookies for some administrative purposes, for example, to store our customers' preferences for certain kinds of products or to store a password so that you do not have to input it every time you visit our website. The cookies will not contain information that will enable anyone to contact our customers via telephone, email, or any other means. If our customers are uncomfortable with the use of cookie technology, they can set their browsers to refuse cookies. Certain of our services, however, could be dependent on cookies and our customers may disable those services by refusing cookies.

**Links to Third Party Sites and Websites Containing our Websites Branding**

Our Websites may contain links to third party sites. Please be aware, however, that EastEssence is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy policies of these other sites or their practices. We encourage you to read the privacy policies for these other sites, as they may differ from ours. This Privacy Policy applies solely to personal information collected by EastEssence.

**Third-Party Web Beacons:** We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here. ](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm)
